Ashley Parker

(912) 614-2045 | ashley@codingandcaring.com

professional summary

I am a full-stack software developer currently located in Atlanta, GA. I have 10+ years experience working with teams and individuals in the social work field and have held multiple supervisory and leadership roles since 2011. My goal after graduating from DigitalCrafts' Immersive Bootcamp is to combine the skills I gained as a social worker with the abilities acquired during the bootcamp to continue partnering with clients to meet their goals.

skills

Leadership Team Building RESTful Web Services
JavaScript JQuery Python

HTML / CSS Node.js Github
React Agile

SQL Amazon Web Services

featured projects

cramIT

- Interactive way for software developers to prepare for upcoming interviews with flashcards and mock interviews.
- Uses javascript, node.js, express, websocket, and postgreSQL technologies

Impactful

- Connects socially conscious individuals in the metro Atlanta area with local charities and allows users to search for local charities using a keyword and view charities based on ratings
- Uses javascript, html, and css

education

Full-Stack Software Development Bootcamp

May 2018

DigitalCrafts

Atlanta, GA

Master's Degree in Social Work (MSW)

Valdosta State University

Valdosta, GA

May 2010

Bachelor's Degree in Social Work (MSW) Albany State University Albany, GA May 2010

experience

Social Services Administrator May 2017 - January 2018 Georgia Department of Family and Children Services (Cobb County)

- Directed a team of 4 social service units in providing quality services to clients
- Provided daily clinical support to social service supervisors and their teams
- Worked closely with internal and external stakeholders to plan and implement strategies for improving performance

Community Clinician

September 2016 - May 2017

Northstar Psychological Services

- Provided clinical services to families and individuals, including counseling and therapeutic interventions
- Collaborated with clients to identify goals and create individualized treatment plans

Family Service Counselor Supervisor

March 2013 - June 2016

• Led a team of 6 family service counselors, providing daily oversight, check ins, and clinical support

Social Services Administrator

August 2012 - March 2013

Georgia Department of Family and Children Services (Glynn County)

Social Services Supervisor

January 2011 - August 2012

Georgia Department of Family and Children Services (Brantley County)

Social Services Case Manager

June 2007 - January 2011

Georgia Department of Family and Children Services (Brantley County)